lillarose.biz 2015-12-06

# 

Lilla Rose And Your Privacy 

Last Updated: December 08, 2012

Introduction 

Lilla Rose Inc. is committed to protecting the privacy of its Independent Consultants, visitors, and customers to its website. Below you will find sections that detail the care for the different types of information we encounter during the course of business. 

Summary 

  * We will not sell your information, period.
  * We may analyze non-identifiable information to improve our site, products, and opportunity.
  * We may share a limited amount of information with third parties to facilitate order processing, communications you have requested, or, for example, tax reporting.
  * If you purchase from an Independent Consultant, they may have limited access to your contact information, and some order information in order to enhance your experience with the Lilla Rose Product line.
  * At any time, you can choose to opt-out of one or more of our communication channels.
  * We require all Independent Consultants to abide by the Federal Can Spam act, and therefore you have the ability to opt-out of their communications as well.

Details 

Lilla Rose, Inc. ("the company", "us," or "we") has created this Privacy Statement to inform its Independent Consultants, visitors, and customers to its website about how we collect, use, and disclose information. 

This Privacy Statement applies to information collected through this website, web based back office applications and tools ("Site", "System"). Except as specifically provided below, this Privacy Statement does not apply to information collected by Lilla Rose by or through any other means, such as information collected offline. 

Lilla Rose grants independent contractors selling rights to its products (hereinafter referred to as Independent Consultants). Independent Consultants are not employed by Lilla Rose. Therefore, Lilla Rose does not control, and is not responsible or liable for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information by Independent Consultants, including for their marketing purposes. If you provide information to an Independent Consultant through the Site, Lilla Rose will have access to it and shall treat it in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Independent Consultants may provide Lilla Rose with information regarding their customers, in which case Lilla Rose will treat such information, once in its possession, in accordance with this Statement. 

If you are the customer of an Independent Consultant, you should check with your Consultant directly to learn about his or her data privacy practices. Please note that we do require all Independent Consultants to abide by the Federal Can Spam Act, and if you believe one of our Independent Consultants is not honoring its spirit, please Contact Lilla Rose directly. 

Personal Information 

Collection of Personal Information. "Personal Information" is information that can identify you such as name, shipping or billing address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, and user name. Lilla Rose collects Personal Information from you when you choose to participate in our offers and programs or otherwise provide information directly to us, including when you register with us, purchase products, participate in our interactive features or otherwise interact with us on lillarose.biz. 

Use of Personal Information 

  * for the purposes for which you specifically provided it including, without limitation, to enable us to respond to your inquiries and process and fulfill your requests; 
  * to send you information about your relationship or transactions with us; 
  * to tell you about products, services, programs, and offers that we believe may be of interest to you via e-mail, telephone or postal mail;
  * to personalize your experience with us including by presenting products or offers tailored to you;
  * to allow you to use, communicate and interact with others on our Site;
  * to help you find an Independent Consultants including suggesting a new Independent Consultant if your Independent Consultant has discontinued selling Lilla Rose products, and to facilitate the business activities of an Independent Consultant;
  * for our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our website, improving our services, identifying usage trends, and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * to allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities (Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that you read these rules carefully);
  * to complete and fulfill your order, or otherwise provide you with products or services, for example, to process your payments, have your order delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service;

Sharing Personal Information 

We will not sell your information. We may distribute information gathered on the Site in the manners listed below: 

  * to third-party service providers who provide services to Lilla Rose, such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, infrastructure provision, information technology services, customer service, e-mail delivery services, credit card processing, auditing, training, and other similar services. (These third parties will be supplied with, or have access to, your Personal Information for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf); 
  * to Independent Consultants, to the extent necessary for them to contact you, fulfill your orders or provide a service to you; 
  * to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, or assets (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings); and 
  * as we believe necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

Non-Personal Information 

Collection of Non-Personal Information. "Non-Personal Information" is any information that does not reveal your specific identity, such as: 

  * Browser information
  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies
  * Demographic information and other information provided by you or our Independent Consultant
  * Aggregated information

We and our third-party service providers may collect Non-Personal Information in a variety of ways. For example, we 

  * collect information such as your computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system version and Internet browser type and version.
  * collect demographic information, such as your location, on, age, gender, as well as other information, such as your hobbies and special interests when you voluntarily provide this information to us. Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you or anyone else.

Aggregating information. We may aggregate Personal Information so that the aggregated information does not personally identify you or anyone else, such as by using Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our customers who live in a particular area. In some instances, we may combine Non-Personal Information with Personal Information (such as combining your name with your geographical location). If we combine any Non-Personal Information with Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

Use and Sharing of Non-Personal Information. Because Non-Personal Information does not personally identify you, we may collect, use and disclose Non-Personal Information for any purpose. 

Cookies and other Technologies 

Cookies: We and our third-party service providers may use "cookies" on the Site. Cookies allow a web server to transfer data to a computer for recordkeeping and other purposes. We use cookies and other technologies to, among other things, better serve you with more tailored information and facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Site. We also allow vendors to use cookies on our website. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies. To learn more about cookies, please visit the following site, which is not affiliated with Lilla Rose: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. 

Pixel tags and other technologies: Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. However, in contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on website pages. We may use clear GIFs (also known as web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags) in connection with the Site to, among other things, track the activities of our Site visitors and compile statistics about Site usage and response rates. We and our third-party service providers also may use clear GIFs in HTML-formatted e-mail messages to help us track e-mail response rates, measure the success of our marketing campaigns, and identify when our e-mails are viewed or forwarded. 

Site Analytics: Lilla Rose may work with third-party service providers who use the technologies described in this section to conduct website analytics to help us track and understand how visitors use our Site. For example, we use Google Analytics, a third-party web analytics service provider, to help us improve our website performance and user experience. For more information and to review Google Analytics privacy policy. 

Widgets, Applications and similar technologies. If you choose to utilize technology provided by us (such as a widget), any Personal Information or other information you make available through such technology may become available publicly, for example, through social media and other websites and platforms on which you may make the applicable technology available. In addition, some technology may have the capability to be distributed "virally" in other locations (for example, a friend or a customer of yours may post the widget that contains your information to his or her blog). Lilla Rose is not responsible or liable for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information and/or other information that is made publicly available. 

IP Addresses 

**How We Collect IP Addresses**  
Your "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider (ISP). 

An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice on the Internet and is done automatically by many websites. 

**How We Use and Disclose IP Addresses**

We may use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, detecting fraud, and administering the Site. We may also use and disclose IP Addresses for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. Please note that we treat IP Addresses, server log files and related information as Non-Personal Information, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. 

Social Network and Interactive Tools 

Certain features on our Site may give you an opportunity to interact with us and others. Contact forms, messaging functionality, and sharing products. When you use these features you should be aware that any information you submit, including your name, location and e-mail address, may be publicly available to others. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit through these interactive features and we strongly discourage you from disclosing any sensitive Personal Information (such as health or credit card information) through these features. If you use these features, your Personal Information may remain on the Site even after you cease use of the Site. 

Third-Party Websites 

Our Site may link to websites operated by other third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with our Site, or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us. Lilla Rose's Independent Consultants are solely responsible for their own websites and for any information collected on those websites. If an Independent Consultant uses an Lilla Rose Site to collect information from you, Lilla Rose may have access to that information and shall treat it in accordance with this Privacy Statement. 

Security 

We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information under our control. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with the Contacting Us section below. 

Choice 

To opt out of receiving marketing and/or promotional offers from Lilla Rose you may (1) follow the "unsubscribe" instructions contained in any such emails you have received, (2) if you have registered with an Lilla Rose Consultant, you may use that Site's "Contact Your Consultant" and request opting out of their communications, (3) follow the "unsubscribe" instructions present on any Consultants (non-personal) communication, or (3) send us a request at the address in the Contacting Us section below. We will endeavor to comply with all requests as soon as reasonably practicable. 

Access 

We provide you with several options through the Sites for reviewing, correcting, updating or otherwise modifying Personal Information that you have previously provided through the Sites. If you registered with a Site, you may view, change, modify or remove certain information contained in your personal profile by using the tools found in the profile section of the applicable Site. For example, if you registered as a customer at Lillarose.biz, you can use that website's "modify account info" functionality to view, change, modify or remove certain information contained in your lillarose.biz profile. You also may submit updated Personal Information to us as set out in the Contacting Us section below. In your request, please make clear what information you would like to have changed. 

We will endeavor to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed or changed. We also reserve the right, from time to time, to re-contact former Site visitors and users, including Consultants. Finally, we are not responsible for removing information or causing information to be removed from the databases or other records of third parties (including vendors, service providers, and Independent Consultants) with whom we have already shared your Personal Information. 

Retention 

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Statement unless a longer retention period is required or allowed by law. 

Use of site by children 

The Site is not directed to individuals under the age of sixteen (16), and we request that these individuals not provide Personal Information through the Site. 

Cross-Border Transfer 

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have operations, and by interacting with us and providing us with any Personal Information, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country. 

Updates To This Privacy Statement 

From time to time we may change this Privacy Statement. Please take a look at the "LAST UPDATED" legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Statement was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Statement will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Statement on the Site. Your interaction with us following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Statement. 

Contacting Us 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us by e-mail at service@lillarose.biz or by regular mail at: 

Lilla Rose Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Information  
PO Box 3117  
La Habra CA 90632 

Because e-mail communications are not always secure, please do not include sensitive information in your e-mails to us. 

Independent Consultants 

**The following provisions are applicable only to Lilla Rose Independent Consultants:**

This Privacy Statement applies to the Personal Information of Independent Consultant collected by Lilla Rose, whether collected online or offline. This information would be collected in addition to any Personal Information we may collect from you as a Lilla Rose customer, as described above. 

If you seek to become a Lilla Rose Consultant we may collect and use your Personal Information including credit-related information to determine your eligibility. 

In order to be appointed a Lilla Rose Consultant, you may be required to enter into a separate agreement with Lilla Rose ("Consultant Agreement"). If you have entered into a Consultant Agreement, we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Statement and the terms of your "Consultant Agreement." We also may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information as necessary to fulfill our obligations under the Consultant Agreement. In the event of a conflict between this Privacy Statement and the Consultant Agreement, the terms of the Consultant Agreement shall apply. 

Once you are a Lilla Rose Consultant (any rank), we may disclose your Personal Information: 

  * to district managers, area sales managers or their equivalent, who may be independent contractors to Lilla Rose;
  * as part of our sales leadership program, to Lilla Rose Consultants who are sales leaders;
  * to current and potential customers who are seeking the assistance of an Lilla Rose Consultant; and
  * as necessary to comply with legal requirements such as tax and record keeping obligations.

We may also combine the Non-Personal Information that we and our third-party service providers collect about your use of our Site (as described above) with your unique Consultant account number. We may use the combined information for purposes such as to analyze Lilla Rose Consultant use of our Sites, in order to evaluate and make improvements to our business model, and for other internal analytics purposes. 

This Statement ©2012 Lilla Rose, Inc. All rights reserved.
